stylemeindia.com 2013-03-24

# Privacy Policy | Style Me India

### Privacy Policy

This privacy policy tells you how we use personal information you provide to us online, via phone or text, by email, in letters or correspondence Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. These practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted and changes will only apply to activities and information on a going forward, not retroactive basis. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.  
**Note:** the privacy practices set forth in this privacy policy are for this web site only. If you link to other web sites, please review the privacy policies posted at those sites.

### Collection of Information

We collect personally identifiable information, like names, postal addresses, email addresses, etc., when voluntarily submitted by our visitors. The information you provide is used to fulfil you specific request. This information is only used to fulfil your specific request, unless you give us permission to use it in another manner, for example to add you to one of our mailing lists.

### Third Party Advertising Companies

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Site. These parties automatically receive your IP address. These third party advertisers may also download cookies to your computer, or use other technologies to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. These companies may use information (including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. Style Me India does not have access to or control of this activity of third party advertiser. We do not accept any responsibility or liability for the privacy practices of such third party websites and your use of such websites is at your own risk

### Cookie/Tracking Technology

The Site may use cookie and tracking technology depending on the features offered. Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the Site, and understanding how visitors use the Site. Cookies can also help customize the Site for visitors. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology; however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties.

### Commitment to Data Security

Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized employees, agents and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information. All emails and newsletters from this site allow you to opt out of further mailings. 

### Legal Disclaimer

We are not responsible nor will be liable to you in any way for events beyond our direct control. Because of the complex and constantly changing nature of our technology and business, we cannot guarantee nor do we represent that Style Me India will be error free, and to the maximum extent permitted by law we will not be liable for any direct, indirect, incidental, consequential or punitive damages or other loss suffered by you and relating to the use or release of your personal information.  
Offensive or inappropriate content on the Style Me India website  
If your comments are offensive, inappropriate or objectionable anywhere on the website or otherwise engage in any disruptive behaviour, Style Me India may use your personal information to stop such behaviour. Where Style Me India reasonably believes that you are or may be in breach of any of the laws of England and Wales (or the law of Scotland if you live there) (e.g. because content you have posted may be defamatory), the Style Me India may use your personal information to inform relevant law enforcement agencies about the content and your behaviour

### Updates

We reserve the right, from time to time, and at our sole discretion, to change or update this Privacy Policy.  
All changes to this Privacy Policy will be published on this page and on the Site. Upon publication, each change will become effective and you will be deemed to be aware of and bound by it. You should therefore review this Privacy Policy regularly to ensure that you are up-to-date with the current terms of the Privacy Policy.

### Privacy Contact Information

If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you may contact us by email at [info@stylemindia.com ](mailto:info@stylemindia.com "info@stylemindia.com ")
